Cindy Chang Front-End Designer

I have been interested in the web since I was 15 years old, making celebrity websites in the middle of the night. I started my career as a graphic designer but have since grown into a Front-End Designer. I love to build from pixel to code and turn ideas to life on the web. I am driven by a desire to constantly grow in my personal and professional life.

Experience

Front-End Designer (Freelance)

2018-present - New Orleans/Netherlands

- Front-End design for various client websites
- UI/UX design for web apps
- Working directly with stakeholders: wireframing, prototyping, design, build out, developer collaboration and troubleshooting

Web Designer & Developer (Domino Data Lab)

2016-2018 - New Orleans, Louisiana

- Lead Creative for the Marketing team, working closely with major stakeholders to create solutions for a rapidly scaling startup in a constantly evolving data science landscape
- Designed, developed and maintained main corporate website, blog and event websites
- Created branding for Strata Conferences and company led events

Graphic & Web Designer (Freelance)

2016-2017 - Phnom Penh, Cambodia

- Worked with various NGOs in Asia to assist in graphic and web design
- Re-branding for organizations
- Web site consultation

Graphic & Web Designer (Industry44)

2015-2016 - Montreal, Quebec

- Lead designer for small web studio
- Designed all websites and worked with developers for implementation
- In charge of all graphic design (business cards, magazine advertisements and brochures)
- Worked as a client liaison for developers and managers



- hello@cindychang.io
- **** 31 0638091532
- cindychang.io
- cindychangy

Education

San Francisco State University
Marketing Communications, 2002

Skills

Design

Wireframing
Prototyping
UI/UX (Product + Web)
Graphic Design
Web Design
Print

Dev

HTML5
CSS3
SASS
JavaScript
Wordpress
Task Runners (NPM, Gulp)
GIT

Hobbies

I love to travel, blog about true crime, bake, do crossfit and watch ice hockey (Go Red Wings).